John H. Cornehlsen Papers 5730
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I: Psychological Profiles
  - Sub-Series A: Profiles done for Companies
    - Company A: Ha, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Company A: Ha, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      Code: 13H
    - Company A: Ha, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      Code: 29H
    - Company A: Ha, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      Code: 26H
    - Company A: Ha, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      Code: 12H
    - Company A: Ha, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Company A: Ha, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      Code: 14H
    - Company A: Ha, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      Code: 27H
    - Company A: Ha, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Company A: Ha, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      Code: 9H
    - Company A: He, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 25)
      Code: 34H
    - Company A: He, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      Code: 15H
    - Company A: He, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      Code: 22H
    - Company A: He, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      Code: 47H
    - Company A: He, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Company A: He, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      Code: 48H
    - Company A: He, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Company A: He, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      Code: 30H
    - Company A: He, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 33)
      Code: 31H
    - Company A: He, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Company A: He, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Company A: He, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 36)
      Code: 36H
    - Company A: He, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 37)
      Code: 5H
    - Company A: He, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 38)
      Code: 44H
    - Company A: Hi, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Company A: Hi, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 40)
      Code: 38H
    - Company A: Hi, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 41)
      Code: 41H
    - Company A: Hi, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 42)
      Code: 49H
    - Company A: Hi, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 43)
      Code: 19H
    - Company A: Hi, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 44)
      Code: 42H
    - Company A: Hi, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 45)
      Code: 16H
    - Company A: Ho, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 46)
      Code: 32H
    - Company A: Ho, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Company A: Ho, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 48)
      Code: 53H
    - Company A: Ho, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 49)
      Code: 17H
    - Company A: Ho, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 50)
      Code: 18H
    - Company A: Ho, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 51)
      Code: 33H
    - Company A: Hu, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 52)
      Code: 50H
    - Company A: Hu, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 53)
      Code: 23H
    - Company A: Hu, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 54)
      Code: 54H
    - Company A: Hy, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Company A: Ir, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Company A: Is, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Company A: Is, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Company A: Ja, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 59)
      Code: 4J
    - Company A: Ja, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      Code: 7J
    - Company A: Ja, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      Code: 11J
    - Company A: Ja, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Code: 12J
    - Company A: Ja, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Code: 6J
    - Company A: Ja, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Code: 8J
    - Company A: Ja, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      Code: 13J
    - Company A: Je, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      Code: 10J
    - Company A: Je, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Company A: Jo, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      Code: 17J
    - Company A: Jo, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      Code: 9J
    - Company A: Jo, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      Code: 21J
    - Company A: Jo, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      Code: 3J
    - Company A: Jo, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      Code: 1J
    - Company A: Ju, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      Code: 5J
    - Company A: Ju, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      Code: 2J
    - Company A: Ka, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      Code: 20K
    - Company A: Ka, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      Code: 31K
    - Company A: Ka, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      Code: 14K
    - Company A: Ka, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Company A: Ke, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Company A: Ke, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      Code: 22K
    - Company A: Ke, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      Code: 24K
    - Company A: Ke, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 23)
      Code: 5K
    - Company A: Ke, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 24)
      Code: 15K
    - Company A: Ke, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 25)
      Code: 27K
    - Company A: Ke, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 26)
      Code: 6K
    - Company A: Ke, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 27)
      Code: 26K
    - Company A: Ke, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 28)
      Code: 32K
    - Company A: Ke, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 29)
      Code: 34K
    - Company A: Ke, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 30)
      Code: 7K
    - Company A: Ke, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 31)
      Code: 19K
    - Company A: Ke, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 32)
      Code: 33K
    - Company A: Ke, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 33)
      Code: 13K
    - Company A: Ke, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 34)
      Code: 28K
    - Company A: Ke, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 35)
      Code: 21K
    - Company A: Ki, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 36)
      Code: 18K
    - Company A: Ki, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 37)
      Code: 17K
    - Company A: Ki, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Company A: Ki, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Company A: Kl, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Company A: Ko, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 41)
      Code: 12K
    - Company A: Ko, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 42)
      Code: 29K
    - Company A: Ko, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 43)
      Code: 9K
    - Company A: Ko, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Company A: Ko, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 45)
      Code: 25K
    - Company A: Ko, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 46)
      Code: 11K
    - Company A: Kr, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Company A: Kr, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 48)
      Code: 10K
    - Company A: Kr, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 49)
      Code: 16K
    - Company A: Kr, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      Code: 30K
    - Company A: Kr, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      Code: 8K
    - Company A: Kr, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      Code: 23K
    - Company A: Ku, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      Code: 2K
    - Company A: Ku, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Company A: La, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      Code: 9L
    - Company A: La, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      Code: 29L
    - Company A: La, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Company A: La, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      Code: 28L
    - Company A: La, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Company A: La, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Company A: La, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      Code: 30L
    - Company A: La, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      Code: 19L
    - Company A: La, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      Code: 3L
    - Company A: La, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      Code: 4L
    - Company A: La, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      Code: 5L
    - Company A: La, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      Code: 32L
    - Company A: La, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      Code: 24L
    - Company A: La, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Company A: La, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 20)
      Code: 25L
    - Company A: La, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Company A: La, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Company A: La, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 23)
      Code: 8L
    - Company A: Le, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 24)
      Code: 22L
    - Company A: Le, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 25)
      Code: 10L
    - Company A: Le, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Company A: La, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 27)
      Code: 26L
    - Company A: Le, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Company A: Le, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 29)
      Code: 14L
    - Company A: Le, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 30)
      Code: 33L
    - Company A: Le, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Company A: Le, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 32)
      Code: 27L
    - Company A: Le, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 33)
      Code: 36L
    - Company A: Le, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 34)
      Code: 43L
    - Company A: Le, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 35)
      Code: 41L
    - Company A: Le, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Company A: Le, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 37)
      Code: 35L
    - Company A: Le, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 38)
      Code: 40L
    - Company A: Le, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 39)
      Code: 15L
    - Company A: Le, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 40)
      Code: 39L
    - Company A: Le, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 41)
      Code: 6L
    - Company A: Li, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      Code: 12L
    - Company A: Li, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 43)
      Code: 13L
    - Company A: Li, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 44)
      Code: 23L
    - Company A: Lo, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 45)
      Code: 38L
    - Company A: Lo, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 46)
      Code: 37L
    - Company A: Lo, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 47)
      Code: 18L
    - Company A: Lu, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 48)
      Code: 31L
    - Company A: Lu, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Company A: Lu, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 50)
      Code: 2L
    - Company A: Lu, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 51)
      Code: 42L
    - Company A: Lu, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 52)
      Code: 7L
    - Company A: Ly, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      Code: 21L
    - Company A: Ly, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      Code: 34L
    - Company A: Ly, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Code: 17L
    - Company A: Ma, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      Code: 12M
    - Company A: Ma, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Code: 9M
    - Company A: Ma, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      Code: 8M
    - Company A: Ma, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      Code: 45M
    - Company A: Ma, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Company A: Ma, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Company A: Ma, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      Code: 16M
    - Company A: Ma, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      Code: 18M
    - Company A: Ma, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      Code: 65M
    - Company A: Ma, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      Code: 64M
    - Company A: Ma, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      Code: 69M
    - Company A: Ma, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      Code: 75M
    - Company A: Ma, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      Code: 63M
    - Company A: Ma, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      Code: 17M
    - Company A: Ma, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      Code: 82M
    - Company A: Ma, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      Code: 21M
    - Company A: Ma, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      Code: 67M
    - Company A: Ma, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      Code: 19M
    - Company A: Mc, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      Code: 60M
    - Company A: Mc, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      Code: 5M
    - Company A: Mc, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 24)
      Code: 59M
    - Company A: Mc, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 25)
      Code: 42M
    - Company A: Mc, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 26)
      Code: 52M
    - Company A: Mc, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 27)
      Code: 6M
    - Company A: Mc, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 28)
      Code: 44M
    - Company A: Mc, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 29)
      Code: 3M
    - Company A: Mc, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 30)
      Code: 61M
    - Company A: Mc, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 31)
      Code: 39M
    - Company A: Mc, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 32)
      Code: 7M
    - Company A: Mc, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 33)
      Code: 47M
    - Company A: Mc, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 34)
      Code: 14M
    - Company A: Mc, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 35)
      Code: 46M
    - Company A: Mc, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 36)
      Code: 10M
    - Company A: Mc, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 37)
      Code: 43M
    - Company A: Mc, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 38)
      Code: 48M
    - Company A: Mc, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 39)
      Code: 57M
    - Company A: Mc, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 40)
      Code: 11M
    - Company A: Mc, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 41)
      Code: 13M
    - Company A: Mc, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 42)
      Code: 55M
    - Company A: Mc, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 43)
      Code: 40M
    - Company A: Mc, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 44)
      Code: 41M
    - Company A: Mc, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Company A: Mc, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 46)
      Code: 15M
    - Company A: Mc, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 47)
      Code: M4
    - Company A: Mc, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Company A: Me, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Company A: Me, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 50)
      Code: 22M
    - Company A: Me, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 51)
      Code: 54M
    - Company A: Me, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 52)
      Code: 78M
    - Company A: Me, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Company A: Me, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Company A: Me, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Company A: Me, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Company A: Me, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Company A: Me, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Company A: Me, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Company A: Mi, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Code: 30M
    - Company A: Mi, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      Code: 76M
    - Company A: Mi, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Company A: Mi, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      Code: 56M
    - Company A: Mi, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      Code: 32 M
    - Company A: Mi, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      Code: 58M
    - Company A: Mi, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      Code: 72M
    - Company A: Mi, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Company A: Mi, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      Code: 79M
    - Company A: Mi, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      Code: 81M
    - Company A: Mi, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      Code: 68M
    - Company A: Mi, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      Code: 66M
    - Company A: Ml, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Company A: Mo, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 19)
      Code: 34M
    - Company A: Mo, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 20)
      Code: 1M
    - Company A: Mo, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 21)
      Code: 35M
    - Company A: Mo, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      Code: 26M
    - Company A: Mo, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Company A: Mo, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      Code: 50M
    - Company A: Mo, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 25)
      Code: 36M
    - Company A: Mo, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 26)
      Code: 74M
    - Company A: Mo, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 27)
      Code: 28M
    - Company A: Mo, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 28)
      Code: 70M
    - Company A: Mo, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 29)
      Code: 62M
    - Company A: Mo, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 30)
      Code: 29M
    - Company A: Mo, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 31)
      Code: 37M
    - Company A: Mo, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 32)
      Code: 23M
    - Company A: Mo, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 33)
      Code: 71M
    - Company A: Mo, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 34)
      Code: 51M
    - Company A: Mu, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Company A: Mu, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 36)
      Code: 38M
    - Company A: Mu, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 37)
      Code: 25M
    - Company A: Mu, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 38)
      Code: 53M
    - Company A: Mu, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 39)
      Code: 27M
    - Company A: Mu, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Company A: Mu, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 41)
      Code: 2M
    - Company A: Na, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 42)
      Code: 5N
    - Company A: Ne, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 43)
      Code: 1N
    - Company A: Na, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 44)
      Code: 11N
    - Company A: Ne, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 45)
      Code: 12N
    - Company A: Ne, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Company A: Ne, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 47)
      Code: 6N
    - Company A: Ne, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 48)
      Code: 8N
    - Company A: Ne, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 49)
      Code: 9N
    - Company A: Ne, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 50)
      Code: 7N
    - Company A: Ne, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 51)
      Code: 14N
    - Company A: Ni, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 52)
      Code: 13N
    - Company A: Ni, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 53)
      Code: 2N
    - Company A: Ni, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 54)
      Code: 16N
    - Company A: Ni, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 55)
      Code: 10N
    - Company A: No, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 56)
      Code: 3N
    - Company A: No, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 57)
      Code: 15N
    - Company A: No, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 58)
      Code: 4N
    - Company A: Ob, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Code: 9O
    - Company A: Ob, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Code: 4O
    - Company A: OC, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      Code: 1O
    - Company A: OD, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      Code: 7O
    - Company A: Ol, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Code: 2O
    - Company A: Ol, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Code: 5O
    - Company A: ON, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Company A: Or, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Company A: Os, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Company A: Ot, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      Code: 6O
    - Company A: Ox, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      Code: 3O
    - Company A: Pa, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      Code: 5P
    - Company A: Pa, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Company A: Pa, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      Code: 23P
    - Company A: Pa, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      Code: 21P
    - Company A: Pa, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Company A: Pa, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      Code: 7P
    - Company A: Pa, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Company A: Pe, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      Code: 2P
    - Company A: Pe, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      Code: 22P
    - Company A: Pe, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Company A: Pe, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      Code: 9P
    - Company A: Pe, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      Code: 3P
    - Company A: Ph, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      Code: 17P
    - Company A: Pi, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 25)
      Code: 24P
    - Company A: Pi, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      Code: 11P
    - Company A: Pi, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 27)
      Code: 12P
    - Company A: Pl, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Company A: Pl, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Company A: Pl, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 30)
      Code: 4P
    - Company A: Po, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 31)
      Code: 6P
    - Company A: Po, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 32)
      Code: 16P
    - Company A: Po, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 33)
      Code: 8P
    - Company A: Po, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Company A: Po, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 35)
      Code: 13P
    - Company A: Po, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 36)
      Code: 10P
    - Company A: Pu, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 37)
      Code: 14P
    - Company A: Pu, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Company A: Qu, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 39)
      Code: 2Q
    - Company A: Qu, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 40)
      Code: 1Q
    - Company A: Ra, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 41)
      Code: 3R
    - Company A: Ra, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 42)
      Code: 18R
    - Company A: Ra, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 43)
      Code: 40R
    - Company A: Re, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Company A: Re, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 45)
      Code: 6R
    - Company A: Re, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 46)
      Code: 4R
    - Company A: Re, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 47)
      Code: 8R
    - Company A: Re, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Company A: Re, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Company A: Re, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 50)
      Code: 29R
    - Company A: Re, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 51)
      Code: 5R
    - Company A: Re, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 52)
      Code: 7R
    - Company A: Re, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 53)
      Code: 9R
    - Company A: Re, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 54)
      Code: 11R
    - Company A: Re, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 55)
      Code: 38R
    - Company A: Rh, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 56)
      Code: 31R
    - Company A: Ri, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Code: 10R
    - Company A: Ri, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      Code: 39R
    - Company A: Ri, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      Code: 2R
    - Company A: Ri, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Code: 19R
    - Company A: Ri, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Code: 12R
    - Company A: Ri, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Code: 35R
    - Company A: Ri, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      Code: 22R
    - Company A: Ri, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      Code: 13 R
    - Company A: Ro, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      Code: 36R
    - Company A: Ro, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      Code: 28R
    - Company A: Ro, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      Code: 30R
    - Company A: Ro, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      Code: 23R
    - Company A: Ro, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      Code: 24R
    - Company A: Ro, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      Code: 20R
    - Company A: Ro, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      Code: 25R
    - Company A: Ro, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 16)
      Code: 33R
    - Company A: Ro, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 17)
      Code: 15R
    - Company A: Ro, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      Code: 17R
    - Company A: Ro, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 19)
      Code: 1R
    - Company A: Ro, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 20)
      Code: 27R
    - Company A: Ro, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 21)
      Code: 32R
    - Company A: Ro, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 22)
      Code: 14R
    - Company A: Ru, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 23)
      Code: 16R
    - Company A: Ru, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 24)
      Code: 34R
    - Company A: Ry, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 25)
      Code: 21R
    - Company A: Sa, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 26)
      Code: 66S
    - Company A: Sa, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 27)
      Code: 2S
    - Company A: Sa, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 28)
      Code: 1S
    - Company A: Sa, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 29)
      Code: 10S
    - Company A: Sa, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 30)
      Code: 3S
    - Company A: Sa, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 31)
      Code: 60S
    - Company A: Sa, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 32)
      Code: 4S
    - Company A: Sa, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 33)
      Code: 5S
    - Company A: Sa, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 34)
      Code: 7S
    - Company A: Sa, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 35)
      Code: 8S
    - Company A: Sa, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 36)
      Code: 45S
    - Company A: Sa, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 37)
      Code: 52S
    - Company A: Sc, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 38)
      Code: 9S
    - Company A: Sc, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 39)
      Code: 59S
    - Company A: Sc, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 40)
      Code: 11S
    - Company A: Sc, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 41)
      Code: 50S
    - Company A: Sc, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Company A: Sc, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Company A: Sc, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 44)
      Code: 6S
    - Company A: Sc, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 45)
      Code: 63S
    - Company A: Se, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 46)
      Code: 14S
    - Company A: Se, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 47)
      Code: 15S
    - Company A: Se, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Company A: Se, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Company A: Se, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 50)
      Code: 20S
    - Company A: Sh, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 51)
      Code: 18S
    - Company A: Sh, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 52)
      Code: 22S
    - Company A: Sh, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Company A: Sh, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Code: 25S
    - Company A: Sh, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      Code: 67S
    - Company A: Sh, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Code: 16S
    - Company A: Sh, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Code: 51S
    - Company A: Sh, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      Code: 48S
    - Company A: Sh, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Code: 12S
    - Company A: Sh, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      Code: 19S
    - Company A: Si, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      Code: 56S
    - Company A: Si, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      Code: 27S
    - Company A: Si, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      Code: 21S
    - Company A: Si, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      Code: 23S
    - Company A: Si, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      Code: 24S
    - Company A: Si, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      Code: 44S
    - Company A: Si, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      Code: 29S
    - Company A: Sk, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      Code: 53S
    - Company A: Sk, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      Code: 54S
    - Company A: Sm, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      Code: 49S
    - Company A: Sm, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      Code: 68S
    - Company A: Sm, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      Code: 26S
    - Company A: Sm, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 21)
      Code: 62S
    - Company A: Sm, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 22)
      Code: 46S
    - Company A: Sm, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 23)
      Code: 31S
    - Company A: Sm, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 24)
      Code: 28S
    - Company A: Sm, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 25)
      Code: 64S
    - Company A: Sm, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 26)
      Code: 30S
    - Company A: Sm, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Company A: So, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Company A: Sp, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Company A: Sp, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 30)
      Code: 33S
    - Company A: Sp, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 31)
      Code: 58S
    - Company A: St, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 32)
      Code: 55S
    - Company A: St, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 33)
      Code: 17S
    - Company A: St, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 34)
      Code: 36S
    - Company A: St, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 35)
      Code: 32S
    - Company A: St, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 36)
      Code: 41S
    - Company A: St, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 37)
      Code: 65S
    - Company A: St, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 38)
      Code: 34S
    - Company A: St, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 39)
      Code: 42S
    - Company A: St, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 40)
      Code: 61S
    - Company A: St, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 41)
      Code: 57S
    - Company A: St, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 42)
      Code: 39S
    - Company A: St, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 43)